I think you need to feel this material for yourself because it is really hard to see
and I can't really describe it but I will try my best presenting the new sharkskin PU material
from Hirokato. You can already see it's kind of the blackest of black. It's really hard to capture.
It is not latex. It is not four letter. It's a kind of PU fabric and I think it looks awesome.
I hope you can see it in a video I'll change it to it don't mind my weird pose I'm just trying to
present this fabric as good as possible with light coming from directly behind the camera
like lots of lights because I find that it's a bit like velvet it pulls the light into it and
does not reflect it back although it does reflect it this is so weird I mean it looks when I look
the mirror it looks like I am completely black but then I took a white pen for some minor
reflections on the outside. I don't know but I love it because it is so black. And also it makes
really funny noises so in this direction it's completely smooth and soundless but if I do it
like this there is this noise so you can see or rather hear that there's a bit of structure in
the fabric and I think that is also why it does not reflect light so much because the light gets
lost in the miniature structure or whatever I'm not expert here but anyway I love this I posted
a reel on Instagram and a picture a while ago and everyone was like what is this material and I was
like it's sharkskin pu check out Hirogato use my discount code because it's just so awesome
I don't know if it helps if I move or not
maybe I'll try it in natural light again but yeah I got the options with
socks obviously and gloves and there's a zipper in the back and as always when I order from
Hirogato it's made to measure I just had the conversation with a friend on holiday she was
like I don't fit into like sizes from the rack and I was like go made to measure especially
Hirogato offers made to measure and I think it's really cool and a really great option to get your
customized fit which is always the best fit okay now standing because i wanted to show you the
back zip here and also that i have a crush zipper because it's really handy if you need to go to the
toilet just order one with the crotch zipper that's the secret anyway and just to show the
fit again i'm trying to move as much as possible because you know fabric and light and whatever
A few weeks ago I was in Bangkok and visited here Ogato and I already saw that this material is going to launch in different colors too and red and pink and also there is purple already available by the time I do this video.
That is so yeah, I ordered a bodysuit in purple and I'm going to switch into them now
I think it's also fit better with like perfection. We'll see
This is such an awesome material you need it in your life if you're like me collecting
shiny or smooth fabrics for nice outfits
Also, it's such a unique fabric. I haven't seen it before
This
intensity so to say
That's why you have to feel it yourself. That's my recommendation
Feel it yourself, check out Hirogato
And this is the purple
bodysuit. I'm just wearing white tights underneath to
contrast it a bit more
Also, I have like a really high cut leg here, which is really nice
And again gloves and a zipper
Now for everyone who is always asking how can I close the zipper by myself, just put a piece of thread through the zipper and then you can easily grab the thread and pull it off yourself.
As you are always curious about the mask options because these suits are customizable with masks or gloves or socks, I have the exact same bodysuit here plus a mask.
and this version we have like a whole window for the eyes and I can also show
you here how it works in the back there are two zippers one is for the back and
one is for the head part that means when you close the back one you can also put
a hood on your head there's also like some hair protection and then you simply
close the... I hope I can show this like this... and then you close the head zipper.
And that's it. It looks like a ghost. Fly away!
All right. All the sounds. Anyway, I hope you enjoyed this video and you know what to order
necks from Hirogato. I really also like the color and of course it works great with my hair
and the red lips and the white. Really colorful today. Anyway, leave a thumbs up, check out the
links in the subscription text, my discount code for Hirogato, my Patreon. Thanks to Hirogato for
sending suits along and yeah, I hope you all have a nice day and I will see you in the next video.
Have a good one. Bye.